<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fourcast</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="token">36a0d86cd5198cc6b37caa6d481a66c0781bdba3</string>

    <string name="pm25_info">
        PM2.5 refers to atmospheric particulate matter (PM) that have a diameter of less than 2.5 micrometers, which is about 3% the diameter of a human hair.\n
        They include power plants, motor vehicles, airplanes, residential wood burning etc.
        Owing to their minute size, particles smaller than 2.5 micrometers are able to penetrate deep into the lungs and some may even enter the circulatory system.\n\n

        A recent study suggests that long-term exposure to PM2.5 may lead to plaque deposits in arteries,
        causing vascular inflammation and a hardening of the arteries which can eventually lead to heart attack and stroke.
    </string>
    <string name="pm25_prec">
        \u2022 Stay indoor and close all windows and openings that allow polluted air to enter, when possible.\n\n
        \u2022 Install an air purifier that is equipped with a HEPA filter. \n\n
        \u2022 When most or all windows are closed, do not burn candle, incense or operate devices that emit smoke.\n\n
        \u2022 Boost your body’s resistance against PM2.5 by increasing your intake of Vitamin C and E.\n\n
        \u2022 If you must go outdoor, use a N95 or higher face mask.
    </string>

    <string name="pm10_info">
        PM10 is particulate matter 10 micrometers or less in diameter. By way of comparison, a human hair is about 100 micrometres, so roughly 10 fine particles could be placed on its width.
        Particles in the PM10 size range are commonly present in air and may be drawn into the body with every breath. In the lungs particles can have a direct physical effect and/or be absorbed
        into the blood. Airborne particles, may also may be deposited in the mouth, throat or nose and be ingested.\n\n

        Sources include crushing or grinding operations and dust stirred up by vehicles on roads.
    </string>
    <string name="pm10_prec">
        \u2022 Setting up public monitoring groups through official channels.\n\n
        \u2022 Reducing the effective inhaled dose of air pollution by staying away from dusty roads and highways.\n\n
        \u2022 Using personal protective equipment like respirators.\n\n
        \u2022 Air quality management and regular reports for work and indoor spaces.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="o3_info">
        Tropospheric, or ground level ozone, is not emitted directly into the air, but is created by chemical reactions between oxides of nitrogen (NOx) and volatile organic compounds (VOC).\n
        Ozone at ground level is a harmful air pollutant, and can trigger a variety of health problems including chest pain, coughing, throat irritation, and airway inflammation.\n
        It also can reduce lung function and harm lung tissue. Ozone can worsen bronchitis, emphysema, and asthma, leading to increased medical care.\n\n
        People most at risk from breathing air containing ozone include people with asthma, children, older adults, and people who are active outdoors, especially outdoor workers.\n
        Ozone is also the main ingredient in “smog."
    </string>
    <string name="o3_prec">
        \u2022 Use appliances with higher Energy Star ratings at homes and offices.\n\n
        \u2022 On very high levels of Ozone, reduce errands and combine trips. Walk instead of drive whenever possible.\n\n
        \u2022 Avoid leaving your automobile idle while running for too long.\n\n
        \u2022 Avoid burning leaves, trash, and other materials.
    </string>

    <string name="co_info">
        Carbon monoxide (CO)—a colorless, odorless, tasteless, and toxic air pollutant—is produced in the incomplete combustion of carbon-containing fuels,
        such as gasoline, natural gas, oil, coal, and wood.\n
        Breathing the high concentrations of CO typical of a polluted environment leads to reduced oxygen (O2) transport by hemoglobin and has health effects
        that include headaches, increased risk of chest pain for persons with heart disease, and impaired reaction timing.
    </string>
    <string name="co_prec">
        \u2022 Avoid burning charcoal inside a house, garage, vehicle, or tent, including in a fireplace.\n\n
        \u2022 Avoid using unvented gas, propane, or kerosene heaters in enclosed spaces, especially sleeping areas.\n\n
        \u2022 Inspect the exhaust system of each fuel burning appliance every year, including chimneys, flues, and vents. Check for blockage, holes, and disconnections.\n\n
        \u2022 Do not leave the rear window or tailgate of a vehicle open while driving.\n\n
        \u2022 Install only CO alarms that meet the UL (Underwriter Laboratories) 2034 standards.
    </string>

    <string name="no2_info">
        Nitrogen dioxide primarily gets in the air from the burning of fuel. It forms from emissions from cars, trucks and buses, power plants, and off-road equipment.\n
        Breathing air with a high concentration of NO2 can irritate airways in the human respiratory system. \n
        Such exposures over short periods can aggravate respiratory diseases, particularly asthma, leading to further respiratory complications. Longer exposures to elevated concentrations
        of NO2 may contribute to the development of asthma and potentially increase susceptibility to respiratory infections. People with asthma, as well as children and
        the elderly are generally at greater risk for the health effects of NO2.
    </string>
    <string name="no2_prec">
        \u2022 While using a gas stove, it is advised to also use ventilation.\n\n
        \u2022 It is important to keep gas stoves and heaters in good repair so they are not polluting extra NO2.\n\n
        \u2022 You can also prevent NO2 exposure by avoiding cigarette smoking and not idling your car whenever possible.
    </string>

    <string name="so2_info">
        The largest source of SO2 in the atmosphere is the burning of fossil fuels by power plants and other industrial facilities. Smaller sources of SO2 emissions include: industrial\n
        processes such as extracting metal from ore; natural sources such as volcanoes; and locomotives, ships and other vehicles and heavy equipment that burn fuel with a high sulfur content.\n\n

        Short-term exposures to SO2 can harm the human respiratory system and make breathing difficult. Children, the elderly, and those who suffer from asthma are particularly sensitive to effects of SO2.
        SO2 can react with other compounds in the atmosphere to form small particles. These particles contribute to particulate matter (PM) pollution: particles may penetrate deeply into
        sensitive parts of the lungs and cause additional health problems.
    </string>
    <string name="so2_prec">
        \u2022 Avoid food with sulfer preservatives.\n\n
        \u2022 Stay away from sites of sulfur or coal combustion.
    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_splash">Fourcast</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
</resources>
